Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of art Womens Committee records, circa 1960-2001 COR0008.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Minutes, meetings files, and reports, 1905-2001; 1957-2001; Series 6
  - Art Acquisittion, 1999-2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Art Acquisition Committee, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Acquisitions (Frame), 1996-1997; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Art Acquisition, $21,000 hold over - Jack Coward, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Albert Landa, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Art Acquisition Review Jack Cowart, 1992; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - April Meeting 2000, 2000 April; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - April Meeting 2001, 2001 April; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Ball 2001, Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Ball 2001, Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Ball 2000, Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Ball 1999, Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Gallery Request for Ball Funds, 1991; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Board of Overseers (Museum), 2000-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Board of Overseers Museum, 1999-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Badar, Susan, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Ball Future Dates, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Ball $30,000 Check, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Ball Proceeds, 1988-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Binstock, Jonathan, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - By-Laws, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - By Laws Members of Gallery, 1997; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Mrs. Bush, 2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Clark Collection Exhibition Laura Pale, 2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Dudley Lecture Agreement, 1984-2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Dutron, Allen Contribution, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Exterior Signboards, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Februrary Meeting 2001, 2001 February; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - February Meeting 2000, 2000 February; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Files Historian, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Friends Benefit-Grand Bazar, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Friends Draft, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Funding Education Susan Bader, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Gehry, Frank, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Handbook - Susan Reed, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Handbook Cover, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - January Meeting 2000, 2000 January; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - January Ex. Meeting, 2000 January; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - January Meeting 2000, 2000 January; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Ball $30,000 Check Raiinmaker A. Express Philip Morris, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Levy, David, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - March Meeting 2000, 2000 March; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - March Meeting 2001, 2001 March; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - May Annual Meeting 2001, 2001 May; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - May Meeting 2000, 2000 May; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Memorandum Confirming WC Meeting, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Membership, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Minutes, 2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Minutes, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Nominating Committee, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Women's Committee Meeting November 1999, 1999 November; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - November Meeting 2000, 2000 November; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - October Meeting 1999, 1999 October; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - October Meeting 2000, 2000 October; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Patterson, Mrs. J, 2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Pin Project, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Phone Mailbox, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Reserved Signs, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - September Letter, 1996 September; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - September Meeting 2000, 2000 September; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - September Meeting 1999, 1999 September; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Special Events, 1999-2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Sarnoff, Lolo, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Serwer, Jackie, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Signboards WC Donation, 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Space (WC Gehry Wing), 1999; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Treasurer General Fund, 1999-2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Treasurer Operating Fund, 2000-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - VACOP Visual Arts Communty Outreach Program, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - VCAM, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Visiting Artist Program, 2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Van Der Pool, Ann, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Wertz, Martha, 2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Year End Reports, 1999-2000; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Washington Post Metro, 2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Loose Documents, Circa 1996-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Events, 2000-2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1957 May 7; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Women's Committee Minutes Annual Meeting, 1958 May 13; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1960 April 29; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1962 January 30; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1961 November; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1962 March 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1962 May 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1962 Spetmebr 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1962 November 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1963 January 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1963 March 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1963 May 21; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1963 September 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1963 October 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1964 January 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1964 February 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1964 March 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1964 April 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1964 May 19; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1964 October 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1964 November 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1965 January 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1965 February 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1965 March 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1965 April 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1965 May 18; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1965 September 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1966 January 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1966 Feberurary 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1966 April 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1966 September 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1966 October 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1966 November 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 January 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 February 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 March 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 April 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 April 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 May 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 September 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 October 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1967 November 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1968 January 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1968 February 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Women's Cdommittee Minutes, 1968 March 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1968 April 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1968 May 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Women's Committee MInutes, 1968 September 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1968 October 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1968 November 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1969 January 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1969 February 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1969 March 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1969 April 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Women's Committee Loose, 1996-1998; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1969 May 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1969 September 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1969 October 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1969 November 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1970 January 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1970 February 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1970 March 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1970 April 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1970 May 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1970 September 29; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1970 October 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1970 November 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1971 January 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1971 February 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1971 March 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1971 April 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1971 May 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 19971 September 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 73)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1971 October 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 74)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1971 November 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 75)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1972 January 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 76)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1972 February 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 77)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1972 March 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 78)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1972 April 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 79)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1972 May 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 80)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1972 September 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 81)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1972 October 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 82)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1972 November 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 83)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1973 January 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 84)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1973 February 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1973 March 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1973 April 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1973 May 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1973 September 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1973 October 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1973 November 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 91)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1974 January 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1974 February 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1974 March 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1974 April 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 95)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1974 May 21; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 96)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1974 September 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 97)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1974 October 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 98)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1974 November 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 99)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1975 January 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 100)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1975 February 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 101)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1975 March 18; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1975 April 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 103)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1975 May 20; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 104)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1975 October 21; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 105)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1975 November 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 106)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1976 January 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 107)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1976 February 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 108)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1976 March 16; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 109)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1976 April 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 110)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1976 May 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 111)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1976 September 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 112)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1976 October 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 113)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1976 November 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 114)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1977 January 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 115)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1977 February 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 116)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1977 March 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 117)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1977 April 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 118)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1977 May 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 119)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1977 September 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 120)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1977 November 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 121)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1978 January 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 122)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1978 February 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 123)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1978 Marrch 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 124)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1978 April 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 125)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1978 May 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 126)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1978 September 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 127)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1978 October 17; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 128)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1978 November 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 129)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1979 January 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 130)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1979 February 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 131)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1979 March 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 132)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1979 April 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 133)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1979 May 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 134)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1979 September 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 135)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1979 October 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 136)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1979 November 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 137)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1980 January 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 138)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1980 February 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 139)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1980 March 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 140)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1980 April 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 141)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1980 May 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 142)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1980 September 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 143)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1980 October 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 144)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1980 November 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 145)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1981 January 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 146)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1981 February 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 147)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1981 March 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 148)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1981 April 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 149)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1981 May 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 150)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1982 May 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 151)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1982 September 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 152)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1982 October 26; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 153)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1982 November 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 154)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1983 January 25; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 155)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1983 February 23; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 156)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1983 March 22; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 157)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1983 May 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 158)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1983 September 27; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 159)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1984 January 24; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 160)
  - Women's Committee Minutes, 1984 February 28; Series 6 (Box 22, Folder 161)
- Lectures and tours, Circa 1950 - 1982; Series 7
  - Docent Committee, 1964-1965; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Docents/Education, 1974-1978; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Lolo Sarnoff, 1969; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Corcoran Gallery Women's Committee from Binder, 1982; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Women's Committee Reports (Old), 1977-1982; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Evening Series, 1972; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Loose Documents, Circa 1950-1982; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Separation Sheets, Circa 1950-1982; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes [1 of 2], 1970-1971; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Meeting Minutes [2 of 2], 1968-1970; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Lecture Series, Circa 1950-1982; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Women's Committee Lectures, 1962-1969; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Legislation - Secondary Boycott Picketing, 1969-1973; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Wednesday Morning Lecture Series, 1956-1957; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Lecture COmmittee, 1958-1959; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Lecture Series, 1956-1959; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Lectures, Publicity - Press Releases Correspondence Clips, 1958-1959; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Corcoran Lecture, 1958-1959; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Lecture Series, 1957-1958; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Lecture Series, 1959-1960; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Lecture Series, 1959-1960; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Lecturer Report, 1962-1963; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Lecture Series Vouchers, 1960-1961; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Art Tour, 1963-1967; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Art Tour, 1960-1967; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Art Tour, 1963; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Art Tour, 1964-1966; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Art Tour, 1966; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Art Tour, 1963; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Art Tour, 1967; Series 7 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Ball files, 1953-1995; Series 8
  - Washington Post Articles 1995-1996, Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Corcoran 30th Anniversary, 1995 April 21; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Photo Album, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Old Letters and Thank You Notes, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Loose Photo Prints, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Corcoran Ball Invitation 1996, 1996 April 19; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The 1996 Corcoran Ball Program, Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - French Room, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Corcoran Ball 1989, Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1990 Ball, Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 40th Anniversary Corcoran Ball 1995, 1995 April 21; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Corcoran Shop, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1984-1987 Corcoran Ball 1988 Treasurer's Report, 1984-1988; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Women's Committee - History, Circa 1980s-1990s; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - The Campaign for the Corcoran Guide, 1988; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Corcoran School Centennial, 1989; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Fashion Show Jeanette Peteite, 1988; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - NYC Trio 1/5/89, 1989 January 5; Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1987-1991, Series 8 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1972-77, 1972-1977; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Director + Staff Correspondance 1976-77, 1976-1977; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Ball = Gallery maps, Tables, Door List 1967, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Women's Committee and the Corcoran Ball 1984, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art Balls, 1973-1976; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Corcoran Ball: 1974, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Ball Lists - 1975, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Loose Papers 1963-1969, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Center Ring: The Artist Two Centuries of Circus Art 27th Annual Corcoran Ball, 1982 April 23; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran News 1967-1969, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - CGA The Grand Ball April 3, 1959, 1959 April 3; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - History of Women's Committee, Circa 1960 - 1980; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - CGA Ball Committee, 1972; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Buffet Ball '64, 1964; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Women's Committee Loose Papers, 1967-1969; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Corcoran Ball 1970, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition Schedule 82-83-84, 1982-1984; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - CGA Women's Committe Lists, 1969-1975; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - By-Laws for Women's Committee 1953-1974, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee CGGA Women's Comm., Circa 1960 - 1980; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Press Clips 1961-1966, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - VCAM Conference, Circa 1960 - 1980; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - V.C.A.M 1970-1988, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - CGA Women's Committee Finances 1969-1976, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Mrs. Wyeth Bills 1983-1985, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Loose Papers 1969-1995, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Sept-June 1994-1995 Minutes, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Women's Committee Membership Lists no date - 1964, 1962-1967; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Women's Committee Membership Lists 1965-70, 1965-1970; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Women's Committee Membership Lists 1971-75, 1971-1975; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Women's Committee Membership Lists 1976-81, 1976-1981; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Women's Committee Founding 1953, Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Women's Committee Film Series 1974-75, 1974-1975; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Women's Committee Corcoran Shop 1970-72, 1970-1972; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Women's Committee History 1952-53, 1952-1953; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Women's Committee Annual Reports 1954-76, 1954-1976; Series 8 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Trips, 1973-1992; Series 9
  - Trips 1983 and 1988, Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Rome and Zurich September 18-29 1985, 1985 September 18-29; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - France and Italy April 8-22, 1983, 1983 April 8-22; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Paris and the Chateaux May 13-29, 1983, 1983 May 13-29; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Milan, Verona, + Venice June 1984, 1984 June; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 5)